Guide to the Bronislaw Malinowski Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Writings, Lectures and Research Materials, 1910-1944; Series II
  - Articles, Introductions, and Reviews
    - Review of East Africa in Transition [a review of the Commission on Closer Union of the Dependencies in Easter and Central Africa] [for Africa ?], [1930?] (Box 14, Folder 103, Reel 6)
    - "The Present Crisis in Marriage," [symposium on marriage], The Listener, galley proof and final copy, 1931 January 7 (Box 14, Folder 104, Reel 6)
    - "Havelock Ellis," Birth Control Review, 1931 March (Box 14, Folder 105, Reel 6)
    - Review of Descriptive Sociology or Groups of Sociological Facts. Classified and arranged by Herbert Spencer. Division 1, No. 4, Part 2-A: African Races. Compiled and abstracted by Emil Torday. In The New Statesman and Nation, 1931 March 14 (Box 14, Folder 106, Reel 6)
    - Review of Descriptive Sociology or Groups of Sociological Facts. Classified and arranged by Herbert Spencer. Division 1, No. 4, Part 2-A: African Races. Compiled and abstracted by Emil Torday. First draft, galley proof, and final copy in Nature, 1931 May 2 (Box 14, Folder 107, Reel 6)
    - "The Colour Bar," notes, fragments, typed drafts with corrections, [1931] (Box 14, Folder 108, Reel 6)
    - "The Colour Bar: A Plea for an Effective Colour Bar," galley proof and printed copy, The Spectator, 1931 June 27 (Box 14, Folder 109, Reel 6)
    - Review of Instinct and Intuition: a Study in Mental Duality, by G. B. Dibblee, in Nature, 1931 July (Box 15, Folder 110, Reel 6)
    - "Culture," reprint from The Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences and galley proof with corrections, [1931] (Box 15, Folder 111, Reel 6)
    - Introduction to The Sorcerers of Dobu by Red F. Fortune, typed copy with corrections and proof, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 112, Reel 6)
    - "Personal Problems," [symposium on marriage], The Listener, galley proofs and copy of a letter to the editor, [1931] (Box 15, Folder 113, Reel 6)
    - "Anthropology and Native Administration," unsigned "leader" [written by Malinowski] continuing a discussion of the issues raised in his review, "The Anthropology of Africa," for Nature, Circa 1931 (Box 15, Folder 114, Reel 6)
    - "Parenthood, the Basis of Social Structure," typed copy with corrections [for The New Generation, ed. by V. F. Calverton and S. D. Schmalhausen?], [1931?] (Box 15, Folder 115, Reel 6)
    - "The Work and Magic of Prosperity in the Trobriand Islands," typed copy, proof, illustrations, and printed copy in Mensch en Maatschappij, [1933] (Box 15, Folder 116, Reel 6)
    - "The Family, Past and Present," The New Era in Home and School, 1934 November (Box 15, Folder 117, Reel 6)
    - Introduction to Law and Order in Polynesia by H. Ian Hogbin, reprint, [1934] (Box 15, Folder 118, Reel 6)
    - "Professor Malinowski in Africa" in Birth Control News, with text of letter from Malinowski to Dr. Marie Stopes, 1935 January (Box 15, Folder 119, Reel 6)
    - Preface to The Cassubian Civilization, by F. Lorentz, A Fischer, and T. Lehr-Spławiński, proofs with corrections, 1935 June (Box 15, Folder 120, Reel 6)
    - "The Foundations of Faith and Morals. An Anthropological Analysis of Primitive Beliefs and Conduct with Special Reference to the Fundamental Problems of Religion and Ethics," Riddell Memorial Lecture, University of Durham; galley proofs, [1935 - 1936] (Box 15, Folder 121, Reel 6)
    - "The Foundations of Faith and Morals. An Anthropological Analysis of Primitive Beliefs and Conduct with Special Reference to the Fundamental Problems of Religion and Ethics," Riddell Memorial Lecture, University of Durham; proofs and final printed copy, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 122, Reel 6)
    - Review of [ Western Civilization and the Natives of South Africa ] by Isaac Schapera; typed notes and two typed drafts, 1936 January (Box 15, Folder 123, Reel 6)
    - "Culture as a Determinant of Behavior"
      See: Series II. Writings, Lectures and Research Materials, 1910-1944 Folder 5
    - "Native Education and Culture Contact," typed outline, early and final drafts with corrections [for International Review of Missions ?], 1936 (Box 15, Folder 124, Reel 6)
    - "Native Education and Culture Contact," two proofs with corrections and a reprint from the International Review of Missions, 1936 October (Box 15, Folder 125, Reel 6)
    - "The Deadly Issue," oration delivered at the Harvard Tercentenary celebration, published in Atlantic Monthly, proofs, 1936 December (Box 16, Folder 126, Reel 6)
    - "Anthropology as the Basis of Social Science," reprint from Human Affairs, [1937] (Box 16, Folder 127, Reel 6)
    - Foreward for Coming Into Being Among the Australian Aborigines by M. F. Ashley-Montagu, reprint, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 128, Reel 6)
    - "A Sociological Analysis of the Rationale of the Prohibited Degrees in Marriage," carbon copy with corrections, 1938 July 26 (Box 16, Folder 129, Reel 6)
    - Review of [ The Origin of the Inequality of the Social Classes ], by Gunnar Landtman, accompanied by letter, 1938 September 6 (Box 16, Folder 130, Reel 6)
    - "Introductory Essay on the Anthropology of Changing African Cultures," Methods of Study of Culture Contact in Africa [Memorandum XV of the International Institute of African Languages and Cultures], proofs and early typed draft, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 131, Reel 6)
    - "Introductory Essay on the Anthropology of Changing African Cultures," reprint from Methods of Study of Culture Contact in Africa [Memorandum XV of the International Institute of African Languages and Cultures], 1938 (Box 16, Folder 132, Reel 6)
    - "A Nation-Wide Intelligence Service," notes, typed fragments, and final printed copy in First Year's Work by Mass Observation, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 133, Reel 6)
    - "The Scientific Basis of Applied Anthropology," [VIII Volta Conference, Rome, 1938 Oct 4-11], published by Reale Accademia D'Itlaia; proof and final copy (Box 16, Folder 134, Reel 6)
    - "Modern Anthropolgy and European Rule in Africa," [VII Volta Conference, Rome, 1938 Oct 4-11], published by Reale Accademia D'Italia; proof and final copy (Box 16, Folder 135, Reel 6)
    - Preface to Peasant Life in China, by Hsiao-Tung Fei, typed draft and proof, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 136, Reel 6)
    - "Prawo i zwyczaj" [law and custom], typescript of article in Polish [for Przeglad Socjologiczn y], [1938?] (Box 16, Folder 137, Reel 6)
    - "An Anthropological Analysis of War," with annotations by the author, reprint from The American Journal of Sociology, 1941 January (Box 16, Folder 138, Reel 6)
    - Introduction to Married Life in an African Tribe, by Isaac Schapera, galley proof, 1941 March (Box 16, Folder 139, Reel 6)
    - "Man's Culture and Man's Behavior," Sigma Xi Quarterly, 1941 October (Box 16, Folder 140, Reel 6)
    - Review of the Cheyenne Way: Conflict and Case Law in Primitive Jurisprudence, by K. N. Llewellyn and E. Adamson Hoebel, in Lawyers Guild Review [published posthumously], 1942 May (Box 16, Folder 141, Reel 6)
    - "Human Nature, Culture, and Freedom," [Sigma Xi lecture at Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, ca. 1940?], published posthumously withe the added title "A Revaluation of Our Civilization", [1944?] (Box 16, Folder 142, Reel 6)
    - "Aping the Ape," one of five proposed titles for an imagined conversation on love and marriage, undated (Box 17, Folder 143, Reel 6)
    - The Dynamics of Contemporary Diffusion, printed summary in outline form [for the Congrès International de Sciences Anthropologiques et Ethnologiques, Copenhagen, 1939?], undated (Box 17, Folder 144, Reel 6)
    - Introduction to [ Africa Drums ?] by Captain Richard St Barbe Baker, two typed drafts with corrections, undated (Box 17, Folder 145, Reel 6)
    - Introduction to a book on nomadism [published in Polish?] by Feliks Gross, typed draft, undated (Box 17, Folder 146, Reel 6)
    - "The History of Kinship as an Anthropological Problem," typed draft with corrections, undated (Box 17, Folder 147, Reel 6)
    - "Kinship" [as dictated to and in the hand of Elsie Malinowska], undated (Box 17, Folder 148, Reel 6)
    - "Misbehaviorism. A Study of the Misuse of Science in Sex" [unpublished?]; notes, outlines, and four typed drafts with corrections, undated (Box 17, Folder 149, Reel 6)
    - "The Natives of New Guinea," manuscript in Malinowski's hand and typed copy of final draft, undated (Box 17, Folder 150, Reel 6)
    - Review of Ideal Marriage, by Theodoor Hendrik van de Velde, typed draft, Undated [ca. 1926-1930] (Box 17, Folder 151, Reel 6)
    - Review [rough first draft] of a volume [possibly Social Organization by W. H. R. Rivers, edited by W. J. Perry] in the History of Civilization Series, undated (Box 17, Folder 152, Reel 6)
    - "A Savage Myth of Incest. Some Results of Psycho-analytic Theory Applied in Anthropological Field Work," draft in the hand of Elsie Malinowska and incomplete typed drafts, undated (Box 17, Folder 153, Reel 6)
    - "Sociology and Religion," essay on Durkheim, first draft in Malinowski's hand, undated (Box 17, Folder 154, Reel 6)
  - Books and Related Manuscripts
    - Argonauts of the Western Pacific (1922)
      - Manuscript; notes on the "Kula," schematic conception of the book, which was originally to bear the latter title, undated (Box 18, Folder 155, Reel 6)
      - Author's copy with annotations and notes, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 156, Reel 6)
      - Copy dedicated to Malinowski's "collaborator" [Elsie Malinowska?], 1922 July 20 (Box 18, Folder 157, Reel 6)
      - Reviews of Argonauts of the Western Pacific
        See: Series III. Writings of Others, 1910-1939 Folder 2
        See: Series III. Writings of Others, 1910-1939 Folder 22
    - Crime and Custom in Savage Society (1926)
      - Rough Proof, 1926 April 14 (Box 18, Folder 158, Reel 6)
      - Author's copy [no. 1], 1926 (Box 19, Folder 159, Reel 6)
      - Author's copy [no. 2], 1926 (Box 19, Folder 160, Reel 6)
    - Sex and Repression in Savage Society (1927)
      - Author's copy [no. 1] with annotations and notes, 1927 (Box 19, Folder 161, Reel 6)
      - Author's copy [no. 2], 1927 (Box 19, Folder 162, Reel 6)
    - The Sexual Life of Savages (1929)
      - Manuscripts: outline of chapters I-VII, notes for later chapters, undated (Box 20, Folder 163, Reel 6)
      - Manuscripts: early draft of Chapter XI [The Magic of Love and Beauty], sections 6-9, undated (Box 20, Folder 164, Reel 6)
      - Manuscript: original draft from which the final version was dictated, [1926?] (Box 20, Folder 165, Reel 6)
      - Manuscript: chapters I, III-VII as dictated and in the hand of Elsie Malinowska, undated (Box 20, Folder 166, Reel 6)
      - Two typed copies of the preface by Havelock Ellis with corrections by Ellis and accompanying letter, 1928 (Box 20, Folder 167, Reel 6)
      - Complete typed manuscript with corrections by B. Malinowski
        - Chapters I-III, pp 1-97, undated (Box 20, Folder 168, Reel 6)
        - Chapters IV-VII, pp. 98- 206 [pp 136 and 137 are missing], undated (Box 20, Folder 169, Reel 6)
        - Chapters VIII- IX, pp. 207-347, undated (Box 20, Folder 170, Reel 6)
        - Chapters X-XI, pp. 348-475, undated (Box 20, Folder 171, Reel 6)
        - Chapters XII-XIII, pp. 476-673, undated (Box 21, Folder 172, Reel 6)
        - Chapter XIV, pp. 674-717 [p. 718 missing], undated (Box 21, Folder 173, Reel 6)
      - Carbon copy of manuscript
        - Chapters I-III, with corrections, undated (Box 21, Folder 174, Reel 6)
        - Chapter XII, with corrections, undated (Box 21, Folder 175, Reel 6)
        - Chapter XIII, with corrections, undated (Box 21, Folder 176, Reel 6)
      - Proof with corrections, undated (Box 21, Folder 177 - 178, Reel 6)
      - Author's copy, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 179, Reel 6)
      - Proof: Das Geschlechtsleben der Wilde n, German Edition, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 180 - 183, Reel 6)
      - Review of The Sexual Life of Savages
        See: Series III. Writings of Others, 1910-1939 Folder 14
    - Coral Gardens and Their Magic (1935)
      - Manuscript: notes, outlines, and early drafts under the heading "Working Guide for Coral Gardens", undated (Box 23, Folder 184, Reel 6)
      - Proof for pp. 1-16 of the introduction to Coral Gardens and Their Magic, Vol. I, undated (Box 23, Folder 185, Reel 6)
      - Manuscript: Chapter I; early draft, typed, with corrections, entitled "General Accounting of Gardening", undated (Box 23, Folder 186, Reel 6)
      - Manuscripts: fragments of early drafts and notes for chapters I, IX, XI, undated (Box 23, Folder 187, Reel 6)
      - Manuscripts: chapters XI and XII, notes, outlines, and typed drafts of chapters on land tenure, Circa 1932 (Box 23, Folder 188, Reel 6)
      - Manuscript: partial typed manuscript of "An Ethnographic Theory of Language," Volume 2, Part Four, divisions vi and vii, undated (Box 23, Folder 189, Reel 6)
      - Manuscripts: fragments [typed and annotated] of working drafts of various segments of Volume 2 dealing with language and meaning, undated (Box 23, Folder 190, Reel 6)
      - Manuscripts: "documents 1-5" with charts, diagrams, titles and indications of their place in the final text, undated (Box 23, Folder 191, Reel 6)
      - Photographic illustrations for Coral Gardens and Their Magic, with captions, undated (Box 23, Folder 192 - 193, Reel 6)
  - Fieldwork Materials
    - Field books entitled "Hanuabada"
      - #1, pp. 1-100; #2 pp. 201-300, 1914, undated (Box 24, Folder 194, Reel 7)
      - #3, pp 415-500; #4 501-600, undated (Box 24, Folder 195, Reel 7)
      - #5, pp. 601-700, undated (Box 24, Folder 196, Reel 7)
    - Field notes [fragments], typed from the five field books entitled "Hanuabada", undated (Box 24, Folder 197, Reel 7)
    - Field book on the Mailu, with notes, kinship charts, native vocabulary, and diagrams by Malinowski, undated (Box 24, Folder 198, Reel 7)
    - Field book fragment, with the following headings: "Bibliography," "Catalogue of collection," "List of objects to be got", undated (Box 24, Folder 199, Reel 7)
    - Field notes on canoe building and canoe magic in the Trobriand Islands; notes written on the back of "The Pearls of Pokang," a story written by Elsie Malinowska, undated (Box 24, Folder 200, Reel 7)
    - Field notes on the Trobriands, on a variety of topics, arranged alphabetically, undated (Box 24, Folder 201, Reel 7)
    - Field notes by Malinowski, miscellaneous, undated (Box 24, Folder 202, Reel 7)
    - Charts, maps and diagrams by Malinowski in the field, undated (Box 24, Folder 203, Reel 7)
    - Journal fragments [period of New Guinea expedition], Circa 1914-1919 (Box 24, Folder 204, Reel 7)
    - Xeroxed copies of journal entries, 1914-1915, 1917-1918 (Box 24, Folder 205, Reel 7)
    - Photographs: contact prints made from the original Malinowski photo-negatives of the Trobriand Islands, undated (Box 25, Folder 206)
    - Photographs of Trobriand Islanders and Mailu, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 207)
  - Notes and Fragments
    - "Art Notes and Suggestions," outline summary of an article, notes and incomplete typed draft, Circa 1921-1922, 1930 (Box 26, Folder 208)
    - Fragment on ancestor worship and its affinity with Christian traditions, pp 39-43, typed [author?], undated (Box 26, Folder 209)
    - Notes on Floyd Dell: Love in the Machine Age, Circa 1930 (Box 26, Folder 210)
    - Notes, bibliographical, on several subjects, undated (Box 26, Folder 211)
    - Notes on class system, undated (Box 26, Folder 212)
    - Notes on "Core and Context of the Coronation," in conjunction with Charles Madge; includes detailed typed outline of Malinowski's analysis, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 213)
    - Notebook containing notes on Havelock Ellis and miscellaneous memoranda, undated (Box 26, Folder 214)
    - Notes on the family, in works by Westermarck, Frazer, Durkheim, and others, undated (Box 26, Folder 215)
    - Notes on Fei Hsiao-Tung and Chinese Sociology, undated (Box 26, Folder 216)
    - Notes on Freud: Totem and Taboo, and related materials, undated (Box 26, Folder 217)
    - Notes on Freudianism and psychoanalysis, undated (Box 26, Folder 218)
    - Notes in Polish of Fustel de Coulanges, undated (Box 26, Folder 219)
    - Fragment: "The Harmonics of Hate," incomplete manuscript, undated (Box 26, Folder 220)
    - Notes on L. T. Hobhouse, G. D. H. Cole, and R. M. MacIver, 1918-1922 (Box 26, Folder 221)
    - Fragment from an index, typed, undated (Box 26, Folder 222)
    - Notes on instinct, undated (Box 26, Folder 223)
    - Notes on "Kenyatta's paper on marriage," from a discussion, 1936 January 29 (Box 26, Folder 224)
    - Notes, general plans, and chapter outlines for work on kinship, 1928-1931 (Box 26, Folder 225)
    - Notes on English and Polish on Kohle, Morgan, Westermarck, and others [re: kinship?], undated (Box 26, Folder 226)
    - Notes on Lévy-Brühl; notes in Polish and French on perception and cognition theories [of Lévy-Brühl?] re: primitive peoples, undated (Box 26, Folder 227)
    - Notes on Linguistics, including "Desiderata of Field Work", 1931, undated (Box 26, Folder 228)
    - Notes on magic, undated (Box 26, Folder 229)
    - Notes on marriage, undated (Box 26, Folder 230)
    - Fragment on the Masai, typed carbon copy, pp. 5b-6, 10-13, undated (Box 26, Folder 231)
    - Notes on William McDougall: An Introduction to Social Psychology, 1923 March 3 (Box 26, Folder 232)
    - Notes in Polish on methodological evolution, undated (Box 27, Folder 233)
    - Notes in Polish and English on the methodology, theories, and field work of various authors, undated (Box 27, Folder 234)
    - Notes on myth: "The Cultural Embodiment of Myth," "The Psychology of Tradition," and "Rite and Myth", undated (Box 27, Folder 235)
    - Fragments [from Myth in Primitive Psychology ?] of early drafts describing the functional method of anthropology, "labelling" and the function of myth, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 236)
    - Notes in Polish on Nietzsche: The Birth of Tragedy, undated (Box 27, Folder 237)
    - Fragment on the Nyakyusa, typed carbon copies, pp. 41-43, undated (Box 27, Folder 238)
    - Notes on philosophy, philosophical systems, Baldwin's "Genetic Theory of Reality," William James, and others, 1919, undated (Box 27, Folder 239)
    - Notes on political theory [not in Malinowski's hand], typed outline of political organization, undated (Box 27, Folder 240)
    - Annotated table, "Psychological Analysis of Instrumental Imperatives," initialed "J. W.", 1941 December 3 (Box 27, Folder 241)
    - Sypnopsis of an unidentified work in psychology, undated (Box 27, Folder 242)
    - Notes on A. R. Radcliffe-Brown's article on law in Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences, undated (Box 27, Folder 243)
    - Notes in Polish on religion and magic in The Golden Bough by Frazer, undated (Box 27, Folder 244)
    - Notes in English and Polish under the heading "Religion, Westermarck's seminar, etc.," includes notes on Durkheim, Crawley, Lang, and Ribot re: religion, undated (Box 27, Folder 245)
    - Notes on religion in Durkheim and others, undated (Box 27, Folder 246)
    - Notes and general plan for "Primitive Man and His World" or "Primitive Man and His Religion", undated (Box 27, Folder 247)
    - Notes on religion: death rituals, undated (Box 27, Folder 248)
    - Notes on religion: food rituals, undated (Box 27, Folder 249)
    - Notes on religion: "The Function of Ritual Acts", undated (Box 27, Folder 250)
    - Notes on religion and magic [containing Malinowski's psychological theory of magic and religion], [1924?] (Box 27, Folder 251)
    - Notes on religion: analysis of magic [black and white], comparison with science, undated (Box 27, Folder 252)
    - Notes on science, religion, and magic, undated (Box 27, Folder 253)
    - Notes on "sentiment in religion", undated (Box 27, Folder 254)
    - Notes in Polish and English on rites and ceremonies in Howitt and others, undated (Box 27, Folder 255)
    - Notes on W. H. R. Rivers: "Survivals in Sociology," includes abstract of the paper and critique by Malinowski, 1913, undated (Box 27, Folder 256)
    - Outline entitled "First Draft of Scheme for Work on Sex Problems", undated (Box 27, Folder 257)
    - Notes on social psychology, undated (Box 27, Folder 258)
    - Notes on social theory: the classificatory system, outline for chapters III-VI of unidentified work; notes on human vs. animal societies, [1924?], undated (Box 27, Folder 259)
    - Notes on "Sociologie in Deutschland," "Simmel" in German and Polish, undated (Box 27, Folder 260)
    - Notes on sociology in Polish, undated (Box 27, Folder 261)
    - Notes on a study of South Africa [possibly Western Civilization and the Natives of South Africa, edited by I. Schapera?], undated (Box 27, Folder 262)
    - Notes on C. F. Strehlow: Die Aranda, undated (Box 27, Folder 263)
    - Notes in Polish on taboo, undated (Box 27, Folder 264)
    - Fragment [of first draft of introduction to one of Malinowski's book] on the Trobriand Islanders in which Malinowski states his intentions as an anthropologist, undated (Box 27, Folder 265)
    - Notes on Valentine re: updating his work on psychoanalysis for reprinting, undated (Box 27, Folder 266)
    - Notes on war, [1934?] (Box 27, Folder 267)
    - Notes in Polish and German on Wundt, re: language, undated (Box 27, Folder 268)
    - Notes on the Yunod: childhood, courtship, betrothal, marriage feast, undated (Box 27, Folder 269)
    - Notes and fragments, miscellaneous, undated (Box 27, Folder 270)
    - Poem and poem fragment in Malinowski's hand, 1912 Jan, undated (Box 27, Folder 271)
- Writings of Others, 1910-1939; Series III
  "Writings of others" consists of books, articles, reviews, papers, a dissertation, and miscellaneous fragments which were not written by Malinowski but were found among his papers. Some are autographed copies; others were annotated by Malinowski. Most of the authors were his students or colleagues.
  The series is arranged alphabetically by author. There are three general folders containing reprints and a folder of fragments from proofs. The final folder in the series contains a list of additional books and reprints located in a Paige box at the end of the collection.
  - Africa, Vol. VII-IX, six articles annotated by Malinowski; authors: L. P. Mair, M. Hunter A. I. Richards, A. T. and G. M. Culwick, I. Schapera, M. Fortes, [1934-1936?] (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Barton, F. R. Review of Argonauts of the Western Pacific, by Bronislaw Malinowski, in Man, 1922 December (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Beveridge, Sir William. "Making History in the Home," The Listener, 1932 February 24 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Clarke, Edith. "The Sociological Significance of Ancestor-Worship in Ashanti." reprinted from Africa, Vol. III, No. 4, n.y. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Dribers, J. H. "Anthropology in Colonial Administration," Economica, No. 20, 1927 June (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Dzikowski, Stanisław. "Przyjaciele Dzikich Ludzi," [article in Polish on Malinowski], Antena, 1935 January (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Evans-Pritchard, E. E. "The Morphology and Function of Magic. A Comparative Study of Trobriand and Zande Rituals and Spells," typed paper, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Fei Hsiao-Tung. Economic Life in a Chinese Village, typed thesis, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Fei Hsiao-Tung. Economic Life in a Chinese Village; partial abstract and evaluation of a thesis by E. Denison Ross, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Fei Hsiao-Tung. Peasant Life in China; "A Note on the Preface of Peasant Life in China, " author unidentified, typed with annotations by Malinowski, undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Frazer, J. G. Garnered Sheaves, autographed for Malinowski by the author, 1931 April 23 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Frazer, J. G. The Golden Bough; Malinowski's copy, with annotations, 1922 (Box 29, Folder 12)